pegaweb.com 2010-05-28

# Pegaweb.com Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us through the "About" page.

At www.pegaweb.com, the privacy of our visitors is of great importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.pegaweb.com and how it is used.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.pegaweb.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Google Adsense Interest-based Advertising

Google Adsense's Interest-based advertising is active on this site. It allows advertisers to show ads based on a user's previous interactions with them, such as visits to advertiser website and also to reach users based on their interests.

This system is operated by Google. Pegaweb.com does not collect or have any access to this data.

## NAI Opt-Out

You can opt out of behavioural advertising here:

<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to this site's users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

www.pegaweb.com does not use cookies.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.pegaweb.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalise the advertising content that you see.

www.pegaweb.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.pegaweb.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
